Guide to the Refuse & Resist! Records TAM.362
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Chapters, 1987-2001; 3.68 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, 1 small flat box
  This series contains material created by and for the chapters established by Refuse & Resist! members outside of New York City. Individual files for city and state chapters typically contain correspondence, brochures, issue fact sheets, and promotional material and ephemera for area-specific chapter demonstrations and events. Material directed to chapters from the national office in this series include general mailings, form letters, chapter starter kits, and chapter reports to the National Council.
  - California -- Los Angeles, 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1-3, Box 38, Folder 10)
  - California -- Oakland, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - California -- San Francisco Bay Area, 1987-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5-6, Box 38, Folder 10)
  - California -- Santa Cruz, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 38, Folder 10, Box Shared Tamiment 164, Folder 24)
  - Delaware, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Florida -- Miami and South Florida, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3-4, Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Georgia -- Atlanta, 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii, 1987-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Illinois -- Chicago, 1987-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7, Box 3, Folder 1-2, Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Indiana -- Northwest Area, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky -- Louisville, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Louisiana -- New Orleans, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Maryland -- Baltimore, 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts -- Boston, 1989-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts -- Central Massachusetts, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Michigan -- Detroit, 1990-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
  - Michigan -- Grand Rapids, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Minnesota -- Twin Cities Area, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2, Box 38, Folder 11)
  - New Mexico, 2000, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - New York -- Buffalo, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York -- New York City, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ohio -- Cincinnati, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ohio -- Cleveland, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Oklahoma, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Tennessee -- Chattanooga, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Utah, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Washington, DC, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Washington -- Seattle, 1996-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin -- Milwaukee, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Mailings, 1989-2001 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
  - General Information Packet Material, 1992, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chapter Starter Kit Material, 1995-2000, undated (Box 5, Folder 11-12, Box 6, Folder 1-5)
- Series III. Artist Network, 1990-2004; 4 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize flat boxes, and 1 small flat box
  This series contains material related to Refuse & Resist!'s Artists Network, a collective of artists desiring to connect with each other through issues supported by Refuse & Resist!. This series includes the initial written proposal to create the Artists Network, meeting notes, event promotional material, and posters created by various artists for the network's Speak Truth to Power project. This series also includes a significant number of files on Refuse & Resist!'s participation and planning for Mumia 911, a national day of art with over 100 events nationwide on September 11, 1999, to stop the execution of Mumia Abu-Jamal. Mumia 911 files contain planning material, event schedules, promotional posters and fliers, t-shirt, stickers, mailers, newsletters, press clippings, and fact sheets about Mumia Abu-Jamal.
  - Address and Contact Lists, Information Fliers, Fundraising, Poster, 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6-7, Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Artists Network Newsletter, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Artists Working Group Meeting Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1987-2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Events -- Announcements and Fliers, 1996-2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Events -- Day of Art for Mumia Abu-Jamal, December 4, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Events -- Art Speaks! Concert, September 19, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Events -- Giuliani-im!: A Quality of Life Crime, October 15, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Events -- Danny Hoch, November, 1, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Events -- A Tribute to the Life and Music of Horace Tapscott, June 15, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Events -- Brooklyn Museum of Art Protest, October 1, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Events -- Just Think Discussion, January 29, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Events -- Unconventional Heroes / Courageous Resisters, August 26, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 4, Box 38, Folder 6)
  - General Information and Membership Fliers, circa 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Logos, Graphics, circa 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Announcements, Notes, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mumia 911 -- Album, Promotional Material, Event Planning, Exhibitions, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8-15)
  - Mumia 911 -- Event Posters (in German), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder Temp 1)
  - Mumia 911 -- Letters, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Mumia 911 -- Logos, Website Planning, Newsletter, Meeting Notes, Post-Event Reports, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5-10)
  - Mumia 911 -- Press Clippings, Venue Files, Visual Artists for Mumia Planning, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1-4, Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Mumia 911 -- Poster and Photographic Negative of Poster Art for National Day of Art Event, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Mumia 911 -- T-shirt, 1999 (Box 39)
  - Proposal to Establish Artists Network, July 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Public Statements, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Rage Against the Machine (Band) -- Benefit Concert Controversy, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Reproductive Freedom -- National Day of Appreciation Poster, circa 1999 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Speak Truth to Power Project -- Posters, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Website Notes, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Youth Network, 1995-2003; 2.70 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes; 404 kilobytes in 7 computer files
  This series contains material created by Refuse & Resist!'s Youth Network, created to organize young people to protest and demonstrate Refuse & Resist! causes including stopping the execution of Mumia Abu-Jamal, reproductive freedom, and police brutality. Material from the Network's signature events, Philly Freedom Summer and Act Your Rage include information kits, fliers, volunteer forms, promotional material, and brochures dating from 1995 to 2003.
  - Act Your Rage Events, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 38, Folder 12, Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Budget for 2000, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Calendars, Event Listings for September and October, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  - Documentary -- A New Generation of Resistance, Overview and Catalogue, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Event Promotional Material, 2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Lost Generation Zine Correspondence, Submissions, Drafts, Issue, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Membership Forms and Fliers and Mission Statement, 1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Event Promotional Material, Statements, Press Clippings, Teach-In Fact Sheets, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - National Month of Resistance -- Youth Organizing Material, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - National Speaking Tour -- Fliers, Fact Sheets, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - National Youth Network Steering Committee Meeting Notes and Agenda, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Scrapbook, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Press Clippings, Promotional Fliers and Brochures, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Information Kits, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 2-5)
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Guidelines, Talking Points, Summary, 2000-2001; TW_TAM_362_ER_5
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Fact Sheets, Brochures, Notes, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - Philly Freedom Summer -- Contribution Forms, Brochures, Volunteer Brochures, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive Rights -- Event Promotional Material, Fact Sheets, 1999, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Resist in Concert! Volunteer Labels, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Student and Youth Day of Action for Mumia -- Information Packet, Promotional Material, Planning Calendars, Notes, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 12-13, Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Youth Network Report, March 3, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)